第三季   第二集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
我才没有利用19位亡者谋取政治利益
I'm not using the deaths of 19 people for political gain.
你在民意测验中排名第三  因此在未来的四个月里
You're third in the polls. For the next four months,
翻 译   凉席
你的每次呼吸都是在谋取政治利益
every breath you take should be for political gain.
祭奠仪式是被禁止的
The groundbreaking ceremony is off-limits.
不仅是那座新的桥
It's not just about that one new bridge.
翻 译   小锤子
明天我们会开展整个基础设施项目
Tomorrow we're rolling out your entire infrastructure program,
包括道路  隧道
with the roads and the tunnels
和一切可以挤满人们的乱七八糟的设施
and all the other new shit they can cram in there.
翻 译  Bella
你在重建美国  而这将成为你当选的理由
You're rebuilding America. It's what's going to get you elected.
- 所以好好利用这个  - 我的天  我有啊
- So use it. - Oh, my God, I have.
过去六个月里  你拽着我参加的每一个短暂访问
At every whistle-stop and fish fry that you've dragged me to
翻 译  玉子酱
和女性派对里皆是如此
over the last six months.
听着  我向你保证  明晚我会在罗利的筹款会上
Look, I promise you, tomorrow night I will scream it from the rooftops
站在屋顶上尖叫
at the fundraiser in Raleigh.
但明早我会当上总统  而不是候选人
But tomorrow morning I'm gonna be the president, not the candidate.
校 对   aiyo
我是不是才跟你说了你是第三名
Did I mention you're third in the polls?
你是这么说了  我雇佣你的时候你可不是这么保证的
Yes, you did. Hardly the numbers you promised me when I hired you.
你不会接受超级政治行动委员会的钱
You won't take money from super PACs.
特 效   小螺号
正确  而且我还不会收私人公司或是特殊利益团体的钱
Correct. And I won't take money from corporations or special interests.
莫斯和波特都拿了政治行动委员会的钱
Moss and Porter are both taking PAC money.
波特根本不需要  他是个亿万富翁
Porter doesn't need it. He's a billionaire.
别忘了提醒民众  他这亿万身家可都是污染河流赚来的
Don't let people forget that he made those billions polluting rivers.
我必须要回到我的本职工作上去了
I've gotta get back to my day job.
- 请吃完你的早餐  - 我还没吃完呢
- Please finish your breakfast. - I'm not finished.
你看过我的副总统候选人名单了吗
Did you go over my list for the veepstakes?
洛林  这不是儿戏
Lorraine, it's not a game show.
是的  我看过了  而且内容毫无新意
And, yes, I have, and I wasn't particularly wowed.
11点的时候注意观察就好
Just keep your eyes open at the 11 o'clock.
- 什么11点  - 摇摆不定的无党派人士
- What 11 o'clock? - Swing state Independents.
你不能未经许可就离开
You're not leaving without endorsements.
噢  还有一件事
Oh, and one other thing.
我为明天做了些服装上的选择
I made some apparel choices for tomorrow.
- 你现在是要打扮我了吗  - 这都来自北卡罗来纳
- You're dressing me now? - It's all made in North Carolina.
所以不要忘了在你的重大演讲中提到这点
So don't forget to mention that in your groundbreaking speech.
我说的话你一个字也没听进去
You haven't heard a word I've said.
我不会在明天的仪式上拉票
I am not campaigning at the ceremony tomorrow.
噢  亲爱的  这就是政治的真谛啊
Oh, sweetie, this is politics.
甚至当你不在竞选的时候  你也是在竞选
Even when you're not campaigning, you're campaigning.
- 艾米莉  你有空吗  - 高级职员会议  已经迟了
- Emily, do you have a minute? - Senior staff meeting. So late.
我知道你沉迷基础设施建设
I know you're crazed with Infrastructure.
这里有百万个环节  而这是你的心血
There are a million moving parts and it's your baby,
所以我想你会想知道的  首次展示中有个错误
so I knew you'd want to know. There's a mistake with the rollout.
- 什么  - 我没有参与其中
- What? - I'm not on it.
我已经迟到了关于这个项目的一个会议  因为我熬夜到了早上五点
I'm late for a meeting on my project because I was up until 5:00 a.m.
确保了最后时刻的每个细节都是完美的
making sure every last-minute bullshit detail on it was perfect.
这才不是个错误
That's not a mistake.
你知道我部门赞助的在费耶特维尔的新方案吗
Do you even know about the initiative my department funded in Fayetteville?
社会创新  将负债转化为资产
Social innovation. Turning liabilities into assets.
首先  我们培训并雇佣了50个被认为不宜雇佣的本地人
To begin with, we trained and employed 50 locals deemed otherwise unemployable
他们拉走了桥上的残余物  并且
to haul away the debris from the bridge, and--
接着是早上好乔  商业部长将会上美国全国广播公司财经频道
...followed by Morning Joe, the secretary of commerce will be on CNBC.
亚伦  你对美国全国广播公司财经频道的话题观点是
Aaron, you have your talking points for CNBS?
强大的基础设施对国防至关重要
Strong infrastructure is vital to national defense.
好极了  你将会和运输部长
Good boy. You'll be competing for eyeballs
一争高下吸引群众注意
with the secretary of transportation...
- 艾  站起来  - 为什么
- Em, stand up. -Why?
会议开始的时候你是不是不在  艾米莉
Were you not here when the meeting started, Emily?
赛斯  你能给她解释一下什么是禁坐政策
Seth, can you fill her in on the "no sitting" policy?
呃好的  就是人们在开会的过程中坐着时
Uh, yes. Um... When people sit during meetings,
会使人惬意  但这是件坏事
it makes us comfortable, and that's a bad thing.
你会变得昏昏欲睡  会议也一拖再拖
You get lethargic, meetings drag on and on.
而站着  我们思维清晰
Standing, we are in and out.
我正试着使我们的效率更高
I'm trying to run a little tighter ship here.
这个理论可以追溯到丘吉尔去
It's attributed to Churchill.
丘吉尔还说过
Churchill also said,
当你处于炼狱时  坚持下去
"When you're going through hell, keep going."
好了  我们继续
Right. Batting cleanup.
美国总统会出现在晨间秀  本地市场的本土分公司
POTUS will be doing morning shows, local affiliates from major markets,
博客  媒体和深夜秀上
a podcast, print and The Late Show.
那天的最后  我们会渗透整个市场
By the end of the day, we will have saturated the market.
- 我不知道这是怎么进去的  噢  - 拜托
- I don't know how that got in here. Oh! - Come on!
我的天  你做了一份最性感的政治家列表吗
Oh, my God, you made a sexiest politicians list?
继续  拜托了  北卡罗来纳州
Moving on. Please. North Carolina.
继续  明天的仪式
Moving on. Tomorrow's ceremony.
保持警惕  我可不想要任何意外
Stay alert. I don't want any surprises.
没什么能让他的言论偏离本党立场的  也就是说
Nothing knocking us off-message, which is...
美国的基础设施正在崩溃
"America's infrastructure is crumbling."
但是总统找到了一条可以绕开国会的办法
But the president has found a way around Congress
建立了价值万亿美元的公私合作关系
with a trillion-dollar public-private partnership
整合了联邦、州、地方和私人的所有资源
combining federal, state, local and private resources.
这是总统的特色计划
This is the president's signature program
也是今天我希望每个人都在谈论的唯一一件事  谢谢
and the only thing I want to hear anyone talking about today. Thank you.
第一  我们逐渐老化的电网带来的威胁
One, the threat imposed by our aging electrical grid.
第二  需要升级以防关键基础设施上遭受网络攻击
Two, upgrades needed to protect against cyberattacks on critical infrastructures.
搞什么
Really?
我没办法在这里工作
I can't work in here.
不管是谁弄的  在我回来前把它复原
Just have whoever did it take this down before I get back.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
肖尔先生  肖尔先生
Mr. Shore? Mr. Shore?
挪威大使想要会见你
The Norwegian ambassador needs to meet with you.
- 什么事  - 跟俄罗斯有关的事情
- What about? - Something involving the Russians.
- 和一个小附属国  - 我可以在三点见他
- And a mini sub. - I can see him at three.
他说如果今早不解决的话
He says if it's not handled this morning,
事态极有可能会升级为国际事件
it most likely will blow into an international incident.
他知道这是基础设施周吗
Does he know it's infrastructure week?
嘿  妈妈  是我  不好意思我没接到你的电话
Hey, Mom, it's me. Sorry I missed your call.
给我回电话吧  我想知道你一切安好
Call me back. I wanna know you're okay.
唐德  轮到你了  你有什么消息
Dontae, you're up. What do you got?
他们已经准备好了你的第一次采访
They're ready for your first interview.
今天你让我和除了纽约里的省钱一族以外的所有人聊天了
You've got me talking to everybody but the Poughkeepsie Pennysaver today.
检查一下第二页
Check page two.
说到钱  那个将一千亿美金投入基础设施的
Speaking of pennies, the private equity fund
私募股本基金
that kicked 100 billion into Infrastructure...
我们在VQH资本的朋友吗
Our friends at VQH Capital?
那里大约有三分之一来自于沙特商人组成的财团
About a third of that came from a consortium of Saudi businessmen.
其中一个  沙希德·穆夫提
One of them, Shahid Al-Mufti,
现在和他的家人都在城里并且想和你合张影
is in town with his family and is requesting a photo with you.
为了33亿万美元  我甚至都愿意笑呢
For $33 billion, I'll even smile.
我会解决这个的
I'll take care of that.
- 人道一点  如果可以的话  - 当然
- Humanely, if possible. - Yeah.
欢迎来到约勒敦
Welcome to Yoretown,
这是一个由于常年基础设施投资不足
where due to years of under-investment in infrastructure,
即将土崩瓦解的地方
it's all about to fall apart.
我可去他妈的  唐德  这太了不起了
Holy hell, Dontae, this is amazing.
是的  这还只是预告片
Yeah. And this is just the trailer.
当你打开软件  就像是在玩模拟城市
When you open the app, it's like playing SimCity.
你可以在自己的社区里游览一遍
You can cruise through your own community,
标记出需要修复或是资助的项目
tag repairs that are needed, projects you want funded.
查看一下我的家乡
Check out my hometown.
不不  别啊
No. No, no, no.
- 好吧  预告天很棒  - 我会修复的
- Well, the trailer was good. - I'll fix it.
在明早之前  弄出一个让人们看了会想投票的成品
Before tomorrow. And make one that gets people to vote.
是啊  我本可以在自己上一次选举中用这个的
Yeah, I could've used that on myself last election.
等等  什么  你没有投票吗
Wait, what? You didn't vote?
夏琳  这是什么
Charlene, what is this?
乔刚把这篇文章翻译给我看  完全是胡言乱语  不值一提
Jo just translated the article for me. It's trash. Don't even bother.
真是疯了  上面没有你的照片
It's crazy. There are no pictures of you in there,
还说他是名草无主
and it says he's available.
我今天没有制定任何人的清单
I didn't make anyone's list today.
我不认为亚伦被这个采访过
I don't think Aaron was interviewed for this,
或是跟这个有什么关系  别杀了他
or had anything to do with it. Don't kill him.
总统做了些注释  我希望安德里亚能直接过
POTUS made some notes. I'd like Andrea to take another pass.
我看了一下你的邮件  你该读读这封信
I went through your mail. You should read this letter.
- 好的  这是封仇恨邮件还是粉丝来信  - 读了就知道了  说真的  看一下
- Okay. Is it hate mail or fan mail? - Just read it. Seriously. Read it.
我给你安排了和新报的采访  两点半可以吗
I have you doing an interview with El Diario. Is 2:30 okay?
没问题  嘿  我也会用英语进行采访
That works. Hey, I do interviews in English as well.
我可能不得不依靠CNBS继续下去了
I might have to bail on CNBS.
我不建议这么做  艾米莉会杀了你的
I wouldn't recommend that. Emily will kill you.
无论你说什么都无法使事情变得更加尴尬了
Nothing you say can make it more embarrassing than it already is.
你和艾米莉之间的事情是怎么结束的
How did things end between you and Emily?
还没开始就结束了  两年前吻过一次
They didn't even start. It was one kiss over two years ago.
这有出现在文章里吗
Was that in the article?
她一直在无视我
She's been blowing me off.
感觉这像是私人事件
It feels personal.
- 你在瞎想了  - 为什么她连两秒钟都不给我
- You're imagining it. - Why won't she give me two seconds?
她有更重要的事情要做
She's got more important things to do.
我不是那个意思  我是说  她疯了
That's not what I meant. What I'm saying is, she's crazed.
她已经负责基础设施的事情几个月了  还有
She's been running point on Infrastructure for months, and...
我不得不去会见挪威大使  我今晚见你好吗
I have to see the Norwegian ambassador. I'll see you tonight?
你的妻子打了三次电话  说这跟骑马有关
Your wife called three times. Said it was about horseback riding?
今天不是个好时候  林恩
Today is not the day, Lynn.
提醒她今天我骑虎难下
Remind her that I'm up to my ass in alligators today.
但首先  给联邦勤务总署打电话并告诉他们停下那些官僚屁事
But first, call GSA and tell them to cut the bureaucratic bullshit
鉴于我们已有的靠政府援助的懒人问题
in regards to our cheese-eater problem.
我希望它在媒体大做文章之前就消失
I need that to be gone before the press gets wind of it.
豆腐渣工程可不是我希望看到的评价白宫的
"Mickey Mouse Operation" is not the headline I want to see
这周的版面头条
about the White House this week.
穆夫提先生  再次感谢您
Mr. Al-Mufti, thank you again.
请代我向你在利雅得的商业伙伴问好
And please send my regards to your business partners in Riyadh.
- 嗨  你叫什么名字呀  - 贾米拉
- Hi. What's your name? - Jamila.
我有个跟你差不多大的女儿  你多大了
I have a daughter who's almost your age. How old are you?
14岁
Fourteen.
你和你爸爸在这玩得开心吗
Are you having a fun time here with your dad?
贾米拉不是我的女儿  她是我的妻子
Jamila is not my daughter. She is my wife.
梅利莎
Melissa?
你又这样了
You're doing it again.
抱歉
Sorry.
你回你爸电话了吗
Did you call your dad back?
他昨天给你打电话的时候  我听见你说你很忙
When he called yesterday, I heard you say you were busy
然后你晚点会回电话  你还记得吗
and you'd call him back. Did you remember?
我正在想办法在被无聊死之前完成我精妙绝伦的审查
I'm trying to finish my lit review before I die of boredom.
为什么你会不觉得分析师是
How do you not find being an analyst
世界上最棒的工作
the most fascinating job in the world?
今早  我不得不四点半就来  给简报员做简报
This morning, I had to come in at 4:30 to brief the briefer
然后他向总统做报告
before he briefed the president.
因为我把其中一份简报弄成程序数据库文件
'Cause one my reports made it into the PDB,
简报员连一半都理解不了
and the briefer couldn't understand half of it.
你的桌上一个私人物品都没有
You don't have a single personal thing on your desk.
你已经来这六个月了  汉娜  是时候装扮一下了
You've been here six months, Hannah. It's time to decorate.
哦  我没打算在这久待
Oh, I'm not planning on staying long.
这是法定强奸
It's statutory rape.
当你在沙特阿拉伯的时候不是的  最起码  当你们结婚的时候不算
Not when you're in Saudi Arabia. At least, not when you're married.
美国需要点文化敏感  总统先生
The US needs to be culturally sensitive, Mr. President.
我们可不就是要吗  这是对人权的侵犯
The hell we do. This is a human rights violation.
- 现在  我能做什么  - 炒了那个审查他们的白痴
- Now, what can I do? - Fire the idiot that vetted them.
他看到了他的年龄和相同的姓  就假设这是一对父女了
He saw their ages and same last name, assumed it was father-daughter.
我也是这样的  别炒了他
So did I. Don't fire him.
- 现场没有媒体对吧  - 没有  我倒是希望有
- There were no press present, right? - No, but I wish there had been.
在你准备开展标志性项目的时候还是别了
Not when you're about to roll out your signature project.
那个王储洋洋得意的改革怎么说
What about the reforms the crown prince crows about?
他通过了女性开车法案却不管这个吗
He lets women drive but won't touch this?
这个女孩现在才14  那她结婚的时候才几岁
The girl is 14. How old was she when she got married?
Thirteen.
老天  她只比佩妮大一点点
Jesus. She's just a little older than Penny.
我有事情要做了
I've gotta do something.
你需要的是一大堆采访
What you need to do is a crapload of interviews.
别提起这个
Don't bring it up.
总统欢迎恋童癖来到美国总统办公室
"President Welcomes Pedophile to the Oval Office"
或是公路建设
or "Road Construction."
你们希望他们发布哪一个
Which story do you think they're gonna run with?
你需要做点什么
You need to do something.
但我们也要保护基础设施
But we also need to protect Infrastructure.
让我捋一捋  看看我们有哪些选项
Let me staff it out, see what our options are.
我们需要修正这个
We need to fix this.
在你开始毁了桥或是沙特资金时
Before you start burning bridges, metaphorical or Saudi-financed,
我建议你和国家安全顾问
I suggest that you discuss strategic imperatives
讨论一下战略要务
with your national security advisor.
你很熟悉挪威与俄罗斯就巴伦支海问题
You are familiar with Norway's 40-year maritime border dispute
长达四十年的边境争议吗
with Russia in the Barents Sea?
是的  我相信你早在2010年就签署了一项协议来解决这个问题
Yeah, I believe you signed a treaty back in 2010 resolving it.
俄罗斯已在该领域发起了新的带有进攻性的挑衅
Russia has aggressively launched a new provocation in the area.
他们声称用于海洋学洋酒的船只和扬塔尔号
Their ship, the Yantar, which they claim is for oceanographic research--
我敢确定那是侦察艇
I can confirm it is a spy ship.
它在斯瓦尔巴海底电缆系统附近徘徊
It is loitering near the Svalbard Undersea Cable System.
扬塔尔号带着两个潜水器
The Yantar carries two submersibles
可以下潜到海床并且有能力切断电缆
that can reach the ocean floor with the capability of cutting those cables.
我的政府很重视这个威胁
My government is taking this threat very seriously.
俄罗斯才没有那么蠢  挪威是北大西洋公约组织的一员
Russia wouldn't be that stupid. Norway is a member of NATO.
攻击北大西洋公约组织的其中一名就意味着向所有成员开战
And an attack on one NATO member is an attack on all.
我们有权援引第5条
We would be within our rights to invoke Article 5.
豪根大使  第五条自911事件起就没有被援引过
Ambassador Haugen, Article 5 hasn't been invoked since 9/11.
这是我们的权利
Within our right.
没准我们有个方法能避免这个
Maybe there is one way we can avoid that.
全国广播公司设在地图室
NBC is set up in the Map Room.
然后我们会返回总统办公室与纽约时报进行座谈
Then we'll head back to the Oval for a sit-down with the New York Times.
- 好的  - 嘿
- Okay. - Hey!
国会摇摆不定的无党派人士越来越不安
Congressional swing state Independents are getting restless.
洛林  我知道他们为你挤出了一些时间
Lorraine, I know they carved out some time for you,
但是总统的安排已经爆满了
but the president's schedule is backed up
而有一些记者已经烦躁不堪了
and I have journalists who are becoming feral.
好的  听着  小菜鸟  我
Okay, listen, newsie, I--
我会和中立人士聊一聊  最多五到十分钟
I will speak with the Independents. Five, ten minutes, tops.
- 我会跟莱斯特说你已经在路上了  - 好的  谢谢
- I'll tell Lester you're on the way. - Okay, thanks.
是什么塞满了你的安排  有什么需要我注意的地方吗
What jammed up your schedule? Something I should know about?
无可奉告
Nothing I can discuss with you.
总统先生  您有空吗
Mr. President, do you have a minute?
据我所知没有  怎么了
Not that I'm aware of. What's going on?
我听说你曾和大使谈论了挪威的事
I heard you were talking with the ambassador for Norway.
挪威方认为扬塔尔号要切断他们的光线电缆
Norway thinks the Yantar is about to cut their fiber optic cables.
- 这不可能  - 确实  但是扬塔尔号
- That's unlikely. - No, but the Yantar
也有窃听那些电缆的技术
also has the technology to tap those wires.
我们在挪威有700名士兵  你的建议是
We have 700 troops in Norway. What do you suggest?
一艘核潜艇  现在  俄罗斯知道美国军舰吉米·卡特
A nuclear sub. Now, Russia knows the USS Jimmy Carter
有能力切断或窃听那些光纤电缆
has the ability to cut or tap fiber optic cables.
我们可以把她送到塔特海岸外的叙利亚
We could steam her over to Syria off the coast of Tartūs--
在那里有俄罗斯唯一的海外海军基地
Where Russia has its only overseas naval base.
也是我们已知的他们的水下电缆所在地
And where we know they have underwater cables.
我们只要坐在这里  甚至不用说话
We just sit there, not even say a word.
让他们体验一下围魏救赵
See how they feel about a game of geopolitical chicken.
聪明  机智  我这就去通知
Smart. Really smart. I'll make the call.
- 洛林  我很抱歉  - 去做好总统的分内事吧
- Lorraine, I'm sorry-- - Go be president.
我会解决摇摆不定的无党派人士的
I'll deal with the swing state Independents.
没准一个大热候选人会就此落入圈套
Maybe a veepstakes contender will just fall into my lap.
好了  亚伦  跟我一起走吧  我需要你帮忙解决沙特阿拉伯的事情
Right. Aaron, walk with me. I want your counsel on Saudi Arabia.
唐德
Dontae!
是我听错了  还是你说过在上次选举里你没有投票
Did I mishear you or did you say you didn't vote in the last election?
我是如此希望是你听错了
I so wanna say you misheard.
你怎么能不投票呢
How could you not vote?
我无法投票给我不信任的人
I can't vote for someone I don't believe in.
那就相当于是投票给了你更加不信任的人
Then vote against the person you don't believe in more.
他们都烂透了  没有一个解决了黑人社区的问题
They both sucked. Neither addressed the issues facing the black community.
又或者是LGBTQ群体
Or the LGBTQ community.
以及  才想到的  科技人群
Or, come to think of it, the tech community.
作为你的上级  我无权过问你投给了谁
As your superior, I can't ask who you're voting for,
但是起码在这次选举里你有投票  对吧
but you are voting in this election, right?
- 嘿  宝贝  - 妈妈  为什么要视频通话
- Hey, baby. - Mom, why the video chat?
我想给你看点东西  等一会
I want to show you something. Hold on.
再强调一次  我不是在问
Again, I'm not asking,
但你为柯克曼工作  你必须信任他
but you work for Kirkman. You must believe in him.
他不是政客的这一事实给了我希望
The fact that he wasn't a politician gave me hope.
我以为那是我来到这里的最佳机会
I thought it was my best shot to come in here,
完成我的那一小部分并帮忙纠正问题
do my small part and help course-correct.
- 所以你会投票  - 前提是他没让我失望的话
- So you are voting. - If he doesn't disappoint me.
你怎么想
What do you think?
- 看起来棒极了  - 谢了
- It looks great. - Thanks.
美国土木工程师协会
The American Society of Civil Engineers
给我们的基础设施评了个D+
has given us a D+ rating on Infrastructure.
这包含了一切  道路  桥梁
That includes everything from roads, bridges,
水坝  港口  学校  铁路  水  能源
dams, ports, schools, railways, water, energy--
噢  我很抱歉
Oh. I'm sorry.
他们同时也列出了一份清单  写明了54000座
They've also given us a list of 54,000 bridges in this country
被他们认为结构上不合格的桥梁
that they feel are structurally unsound.
好吧  也不算很多
Well, minus one.
北卡罗来纳州费耶特维尔的那座桥也上了榜
The bridge from Fayetteville, North Carolina was on that list.
因为我们  政府  没有很好地团结
Nineteen senseless deaths because we, the government, couldn't come together
履行我们保护公民的基本义务  导致了十九个毫无意义的牺牲
and perform our most basic responsibility, which is to protect its citizens.
但是明日我们即将开始全国范围内的重建
But tomorrow we start rebuilding again. Nationwide.
我和总统在一起
I am with the president.
林恩  冷静一下  好吗  听我说  离开商场  回家
Lynn, calm down, okay? Listen to me. Leave the store. Go home.
好的  什么也别做  我现在就过去
Okay, just do not do anything else. I'm leaving now.
长官  你还好吗
Sir? Are you okay?
我相信你已经听说了最近的老鼠目击事件
I take it you've heard about the latest mouse sighting.
问题是  白宫是个历史性地标建筑
The trouble is, the White House is a historical landmark--
- 我要离开一下  - 现在吗
- I'm going off campus. - Now?
但是你的安排都满了  总统知道此事吗
But your schedule is jammed. Is the president aware?
是的
Yeah.
当你想到一些这片土地上的标志性的建筑时
When you think of some of the iconic structures across this land...
布鲁克林大桥  金色大门大桥
The Brooklyn Bridge, the Golden Gate Bridge,
胡佛大坝  都是由有远见的异议者想象出来的  好吧
the Hoover Dam, imagined by visionary mavericks. Well...
你知道是谁给我们的州际系统的吗
Do you know who gave us our US Interstate system?
不准作弊
No cheating.
德怀特·艾森豪威尔  1956年
Dwight Eisenhower, 1956.
国家州际公路和国防公路法
The National Interstate and Defense Highway Act.
注意他的用词是  防
Notice his use of the word "defense."
艾森豪威尔总统相信这对我们的国防至关重要
President Eisenhower believed it was crucial to our national security,
而我赞同他的看法
and I agree with him.
半岛电视台报道了你于今天早些时候会见了一名主要投资人
Al Jazeera is reporting you met with a key investor
在你的P3基金  沙希德·穆夫提  这是真的吗  长官
in your P3 fund earlier today. Shahid Al-Mufti. Is that true, sir?
是的  这是真的
Yes, that's correct.
他们还放出一张你微笑着
They posted a smiling picture of you
与沙希德·穆夫提及其14岁妻子的合影
posing with Al-Mufti and his 14-year-old wife.
你赞同这段关系吗  总统先生
You condone this relationship, Mr. President?
不  当然不
No, of course I don't.
我最近听说在发展中国家
I've recently learned that in developing countries,
每三个女孩中就有一个会在18岁前结婚
one in three girls are married before they reach the age of 18.
而有些甚至早在10岁就结婚了
Some as young as ten.
我有一个11岁的女儿
I have an 11-year-old daughter
而我无法想象如果她处在那个境地会怎么样
and I can't imagine her being put in that position.
我觉得童婚是原始而又野蛮的
I think childhood marriage is barbaric.
但我听说王储正在着手改革
But I am told that the crown prince is trying to reform.
我只能督促他更加努力加快进程
I can only urge him to try harder.
诉讼期间的抚养费
Alimony pendente lite.
是指未决诉讼
It means "pending the litigation."
亲爱的  让你的律师来说这些术语吧
Sweetie, let your attorney handle the big words.
我以为我们同意文明点
I thought we agreed to be civil.
那是在你要求在我们已经争论了一整年
That was before you demanded money on top of the money
的数额上再次加钱之前的事
that we've been arguing about for over a year.
这是暂时的  法院说赚钱更少的伴侣是
It's temporary. The court says the spouse making less money is--
有权过我和你在一起时已经习惯的生活方式
Is entitled to keep living the lifestyle that I accustomed you to.
我发誓  艾伦  有时候我觉得你和我在一起只是为了钱
I swear, Alan, sometimes I think you only wanted me for my money.
我们已经结束了
We're done.
你知道的  我的其他两个前夫都没有要求赡养费
You know, my other two exes didn't ask for alimony.
噢  是的  他们都有工作
Oh, right, they had jobs.
法官会保证这个的  洛林
The judge will grant it, Lorraine.
你有时间耗在这上面打官司吗
Do you have time to spend in court fighting this?
该死
Shit.
他们和沙特大使谈过了
They talked to the Saudi Embassy.
王储宾·扎拉尼十分气愤
Crown Prince bin Zahrani is royally pissed. Literally.
我很清楚  他们只是发出声明
I'm aware. They just released a statement.
王储宾·扎拉尼认为柯克曼总统的言论
"Crown Prince Ibrihim bin Zahrani considers President Kirkman's remarks
对王国来说是个不可接受的侮辱
an unacceptable affront to the Kingdom."
他们威胁说要撤走所有的贸易和投资交易
They're threatening to pull out of trade and investment deals,
也威胁说要把大使驱逐出境  还有很多
threatening to expel the ambassador. The list goes on.
取消总统今日的其余媒体采访
Pull the rest of POTUS' press appearances.
他一整天都会被沙特大使的问题炮轰的
He's gonna be stuck all day with the Saudi ambassador.
我很抱歉我真的越界了
I'm sorry I really stepped in it.
看到你不在会发生什么了吧  马斯
See what happens when you're not around, Mars?
真诚地道歉  总统先生  我真的不该离开那个房间的
I apologize, Mr. President. I never should have left that room.
除了没有阻止我  把袜子塞在我嘴里
Short of tackling me and sticking a sock in my mouth,
这都是特勤处希望枪毙你的理由
which the Secret Service would have shot you for,
真的没有什么你能做的了  你还好吗
there's really nothing you could do. Are you okay?
是的  我还好  林恩才是病倒的那个
Yeah, I'm fine. It's Lynn, she's sick.
但她很快就会好起来的  我得去药店了
But she's gonna be fine. I just have to stop by the pharmacy.
我会尽快赶回来的
I'll be back as soon as I can.
做你需要的做的事吧  我希望她能快点恢复健康
Do what you need to do. I hope she feels better soon.
我也希望
Me, too.
在你按照我的药方配好药之前  我是绝不会再次让步的
I'm not stepping aside again until you fill my prescription.
- 哈普太太  我不能这么做  - 别废话  快配药
- Mrs. Harper, I can't. - Just fill it.
这儿有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
他拒绝按我的药方配药
He's refusing to fill my prescription.
这药方完全合法
It's a legitimate script.
她正在被脊髓损伤导致的慢性疼痛折磨
She has chronic pain from a spinal injury.
我很乐意在五天之内填好它  直到它过期为止
I'll be happy to fill it in five days, when it's due.
林恩  我很抱歉   我早应该想到的
Lynn, I'm sorry. I should have counted.
我来这儿之前给你打了三次电话
I called you three times before I came here.
你一次都没回我
You didn't call back.
- 真是我们经历过最糟糕的一天了  - 又不是我选的
- You couldn't have picked a worse day. - I didn't pick it.
我都要疼死了
I'm in pain.
在此期间你就不能给她点什么药物止痛吗
Is there something you can give her in the interim?
- 只要不是芬太尼就行  - 只有它管用
- Something other than fentanyl. - Nothing else works.
- 好了  林恩  我们现在得走了  - 不
- Okay, Lynn, we have to go now. - No.
林恩  对不起  林恩  我们真得走了
Lynn... Excuse me. Lynn, we need to go.
该死的手机摄像头  她准会把它卖给TMZ
Fucking cell phone cameras. She'll sell it to TMZ.
宰赫拉尼公主  欢迎
Princess Zahrani, welcome.
总统先生  谢谢你能接见我
Thank you for receiving me, Mr. President.
请坐
Please.
我以沙特阿拉伯王国大使馆顾问的身份
I'm here in my capacity as Counselor of the Embassy
来到这里拜访你
of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.
请叫我拉尼亚
Please, call me Rania.
坦白说  当他们告诉我
I have to be honest. I was very surprised
阿拉维大使派你过来时  我很惊讶
when I was told that Ambassador Alawi was sending you in his place.
为沙特阿拉伯居然允许女人工作而惊讶吗
Surprised that Saudi Arabia allows women to work at all?
我向你保证  我的消息可没有那么不灵通
I assure you I'm not that ill-informed.
我恰恰是被派来调查你的消息有多灵通的
I was sent to find out how informed you are.
所以我们先讲清楚  穆夫提并不等同于整个私募股权基金
So, make it clear that Al-Mufti is not the private equity fund.
他仅仅是微不足道的沧海一粟而已
He's just a part of a part of it.
而私募股权基金本身也仅仅是基础设施基金的一部分
And the private equity fund itself is just part of the infrastructure fund.
是什么让他变成了一部分中的一部分中的一部分呢
Which makes him a part of a part of a part of it.
这不重要
That's not gonna matter.
只要尽你所能  让他们能通过沙特阿拉伯就好
Just do whatever you can to move them past Saudi Arabia.
在沙特阿拉伯  女人同样可以接受教育
In Saudi Arabia, women are also allowed to attend school.
当然  要先经过男人的允许
Yes, with the permission of a man.
王储正在积极缩减监护制度的规模
The crown prince is actively scaling back the guardianship system.
我进入乔治华盛顿大学时
When I enrolled in George Washington University,
我没获得任何男性的许可
I required no man's permission.
恕我直言  你可是王储的堂姐啊
With all due respect, you're the crown prince's cousin.
你知道我们的皇室家族有多少名成员吗
Do you know how many members of the royal family there are?
- 这我一时可想不起来  不  我不知道  - 一万五千人
- Off the top of my head, no. - Fifteen thousand.
我们两国在很多问题上都存在分歧
There are many issues on which our countries diverge,
我们也都认定还存在将我们联系在一起的纽带
and we both understand the ties that bind us together.
我们要如何修复这条纽带呢
What can we do to fix this?
你知不知道你让我堂弟的改革
Do you have any idea how much harder you've made it for my cousin
受到多少强硬派的阻挠
to get reforms past the hardliners?
现在  他做任何事看起来都像是在听从美国人的命令
Anything he does now will look like he's doing America's bidding.
我不确定这个问题能否修复
I'm not sure if it is fixable.
我需要你立刻启动有力的损害控制
I need you to jump on damage control.
我已经在去圆石滩的路上了
I'm on my way to Pebble Beach.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我假设我再也不用谈基础设施了  对不对
I assume I'm not talking about infrastructure anymore, right?
计划有变
Change of plans.
我需要你来恢复中东的和平稳定
I need you to restore peace in the Middle East.
对于我的公开发言  我感到非常抱歉
I'm very sorry for what I said publicly.
我应该将我的担忧告诉王储本人
I should have shared my concerns with the crown prince himself.
因为世界上其他国家如何行动
Because it is up to the morally superior America
全有赖于道德水准崇高的美国的教导
to teach the rest of the world how to act.
不  因为我相信每个小女孩都有权拥有自己的童年
No, because I believe every young girl has a right to a childhood.
穆夫提并不为这家主权财富基金会工作
Al-Mufti does not work for the sovereign wealth fund.
我的国家绝不会给男人送去一个未成年的妻子
The Kingdom would never have sent a man with an underaged wife.
这是因为你的眼睛会被欺骗  并不因为它不存在
Because the optics would've been bad, not because it doesn't exist.
我的笔哪儿去了
Where's my pen?
赛斯  我马上要去看简报
Seth, I'm gonna watch the briefing.
现在童婚在我们的城市里很少见
Child marriage is now uncommon in our cities.
它确实存在  但在某些地方  人们需要更长时间才能完成观念的变革
It exists, but in places where change takes longer to reach.
比如部落首领统治下的农村地区  追随极端神职人员的信徒
Rural areas under tribal chiefs, adherents of extreme clerics.
你看不到那些女孩  并不意味她们就不重要
Just because those girls are out of sight doesn't mean they don't matter.
请告诉我  除此之外  你假设沙特阿拉伯还有什么问题
Please, tell me. What else do you assume is wrong with Saudi Arabia?
我试着不去假设  因此我要告诉你我所知道的情况
I try not to assume, so I'll tell you what I know.
911事件中的19名劫机者里  有15名是沙特公民
Fifteen of the 19 hijackers from 9/11 were Saudi nationals.
你们的宗教警察宁愿看着女孩们被活活烧死
Your religious police would prefer to watch girls burn to death in their school
也让她们脱掉罩袍走出学校
than leave it without their burqas on.
你们迫害宗教少数派  女性活动家
You persecute religious minorities, female activists.
你们没有新闻自由  历史里遍布酷刑的阴影
You have no free press, a long history of torture.
你们谋杀那些胆敢公开反对你们的记者
And you murder journalists that speak out against you.
你们对我们所知甚少
You know a little about us,
- 但我们足够了解你们  - 比如
- but we know so much more about you. -Such as?
我们知道你的国家建立在奴隶制的基础上
We know your country was founded as a slave state.
你们的监禁率在全世界位列第一
Your incarceration rate is the highest in the world.
你们的人口总数还不到世界人口的5%
You're less than 5% of the world's population,
却关押着全世界22%的罪犯
yet you house 22% of the world's criminals.
你们会因吸食大麻而被送入监牢
You give prison sentences for smoking marijuana,
却不会为诈骗数十亿美元得到应有的刑罚
but not for billion-dollar fraud.
让没有罪的人扔第一块石头  我同意
"Let he who is without sin cast the first stone." Point taken.
这只是个开始
I'm just getting started.
沙特阿拉伯犹如中东的制轮楔
Saudi Arabia is the linchpin of the Middle East.
它是维持中东地区稳定的关键
It's the key to its stability.
他们帮助我们打击猖獗的基地组织和ISIS
They help fight al-Qaeda and ISIS in the region.
他们已经成功阻止了多起针对美国的恐怖主义阴谋
They've stopped numerous terrorist plots against America.
事实上  正由于我们和沙特阿拉伯建立了亲密关系  我们才更安全
The truth is, we're safer because of our relationship with Saudi Arabia.
你们的谋杀案数量简直是个天文数字
Your murder rate is astronomical.
全世界的民用手枪
Of all the civilian-owned handguns in the world,
整整一半都由美国人持有
Americans own nearly half.
你们自称是全球最伟大的国家
You call yourself the greatest country in the world,
却任由50万国民流离失所  无家可归
yet you allow 500,000 of your people to go homeless,
数百万人缺乏医疗保障
millions to go without health care.
作为一个美国公民  美国有很多事情让我无法为之骄傲
As an American, these are things I am not proud of.
总统将永远捍卫人文主义价值观  克莱尔
The president will always stand up for humanistic values. Claire.
柯克曼总统对童婚持什么态度呢
Where does President Kirkman stand on child marriage?
对于沙希德·穆夫提的婚姻状况  总统并不知情
The president was unaware of Shahid Al-Mufti's marital status.
在你因我们允许童婚而义愤填膺地指责我们之前
Before you rain righteous indignation on us for allowing child marriage,
看看你自己的国家吧
look in your backyard.
什么
Excuse me?
让我再说清楚一些  他在美国如何看待童婚
Let me clarify. Where does he stand on child marriage in the US?
我不明白
I don't follow.
你知道美国也允许小孩子结婚吗?
You're aware America also allows children to marry?
事实并非如此  好好翻查50个州的法律吧
That's not true. Go ahead and check the statutes in all 50 states.
在这个国家  法定结婚年龄最低是18岁
The minimum age at which people can get married by law in this country is 18,
18岁后  你就不会再被大家当成未成年人了
18 being the age at which you're no longer considered a minor.
因此我们没有童婚
Ergo, no child marriage.
- 那有人钻法律漏洞怎么办呢？  - 什么漏洞
- What about loopholes? - What loopholes?
48个州的法律都有允许未成年人结婚的漏洞
Forty-eight states have loopholes allowing minors to marry...
16岁和17岁的青少年有父母的许可
16 and 17-year-olds with parental permission.
15岁及以下的儿童需要法官批准
Children 15 and younger require a judge's approval,
这些都要符合法律规定才能被授予
which is routinely granted.
我回头再跟你说
I'll get back to you on that.
也就是说  总统在其他国家是反对童婚的
So, the president is against child marriage in other countries,
但在自己的国家就无所谓了
but fine with it here?
我不能针对国家安全委员会职权范围之外的问题
I can't speak with authority
做出任何权威的回答
to issues outside the purview of the National Security Council,
但我可以明确地为柯克曼总统的人格做出担保
but what I can unequivocally vouch for is President Kirkman's character.
他生来就学不会虚伪
Hypocrisy is not in his DNA.
如果美国有不公正的事情存在  他会尽己所能去纠正  去改变
If there's an injustice involved, he'll do everything within his power to right it.
我有个问题
I have a question about the president's trip
关于总统明天去北卡罗来纳州的行程
to North Carolina tomorrow.
好的  菲尔  你想知道什么
Yes, Phil. What would you like to know?
在北卡罗莱纳州
Is the president aware
14岁及以下的儿童在分娩或怀孕的情况下都能领结婚证
that North Carolina allows children as young as 14
请问总统对此是否知情
to obtain a marriage license in the case of childbirth or pregnancy?
现在让所有人都进来  谢谢
Get everyone in here now. Thank you.
还有针对其余议题的其他问题吗
Are there any other questions on any other topic?
在我每天的合成生物学综述里
In my daily lit review on synthetic biology,
它通常都会让我无比厌烦
which normally bores the tits off of me,
我找到了一位生物遗传学家  他给罂粟的整个基因组都进行了测序
I found a biogeneticist who sequenced the entire genome of the poppy.
我很高兴你终于开始享受你的分析工作了
I'm really happy you're finally enjoying your work in Analysis.
这是我起步的地方
It's where I started.
在罂粟花丛中生长的罂粟  在阿富汗生长的罂粟
The poppy as in opium poppy, as in grown in Afghanistan.
制造出资助恐怖主义的海洛因
Makes heroin that funds terrorism.
现在测序已经完成了
Now that it's sequenced,
我们的人可以顺利进入  并用CRISPR剪接编辑这个基因组
our guys can go in and use CRISPR to splice and edit this genome
彻底摧毁他们所有该死的作物
and wipe out their entire fucking crop.
这位生物遗传学家是我们的人吗  在美国国防部高级研究计划局还是美国疾病控制与预防中心
This biogeneticist, is he one of ours? DARPA? CDC?
伊莱梅斯博士  这家伙来自个人独立生物实验室
Dr. Eli Mays. This guy crowdsourced from a DIY bio lab.
一个生物黑客
A biohacker.
我们需要先和他保持联系  得抢在某些不友好的家伙之前
We need to make contact before an unfriendly does.
干得漂亮  汉娜  把它写进你的日常报告里吧
This is very good work, Hannah. Put it in your daily report.
把它交给你的主管  他们会为你惊叹的
Give it to your supervisor. They'll be very impressed.
黛安  我并不想记录这件事
Dianne, I don't want to just write it up.
是我发现了他  他应该归我管
I discovered him. He should be mine.
汉娜  你有过工作以外的生活吗
Hannah, do you have a life outside of work?
- 这和我们正在讨论的事有什么关系  - 你知道的  比如爱好  人际交流这些
- What does this have to with-- - You know, hobbies, human interactions?
我每周末都会去一个遛狗公园
There's a dog park I go to on the weekend.
- 哦  你养了一只狗吗  - 我没养
- Oh, you have a dog? - No.
黛安  让我进入行动组吧
Dianne, put me in Operations.
但你刚在分析方面迈出了一大步
But you're just hitting your stride in Analysis.
我知道你招募我来  并不是让我整天在桌子后边呆坐着的
I know you didn't just recruit me to sit behind a desk.
这是个测试  对不对
This has been a test, right?
用惩罚我或打击我的方式进行测试  现在我完成了任务
To punish me or break me. Mission accomplished.
我在地狱般的折磨里度过了六个月  我依然情绪稳定精神正常
I've been in hell for six months. I've been good.
如果我没得到这个机会  我马上就去杀了梅丽莎
And if I don't get out, I'm gonna kill Melissa.
你说得对
You're right.
我们只是把你浸泡在消毒水里
We sheep-dipped you.
中央情报局不是执法机构
The CIA is not law enforcement.
我们是情报收集者  我们没有枪
We are intelligence gatherers. No gun.
你这是同意我去参加行动了吗
You're moving me to Operations?
你不会后悔的
You will not regret it.
- 我只希望让你明白  - 伊莎贝尔  不是现在
- I just wanted to let you know-- - Not now, Isabel.
我们现在可是一团乱麻啊  我正要去见总统呢
We're in the middle of a clusterfuck. I'm on my way to see POTUS.
这可不关我的事
This isn't about my initiative--
让我歇一会儿吧
Give it a break already.
我知道你有多想坐在管事儿的人中间
I know how badly you want a seat at the big kids' table.
我也经历过  我明白你怎么想的
I've been there. I get it.
我一直在指导女性  我也会尽我所能帮助你
I'm all about mentoring women, and I will do whatever I can for you.
但今天绝对不行
But it's not happening today.
我在的那个组织  我们处理莫桑比克的未成年新娘的相关事宜
The NGO I was with, we worked with child brides in Mozambique.
从2000年到2016年
From the year 2000 to the year 2015,
这个国家有超过20万起童婚
there were over 200,000 child marriages in this country.
这怎么不在我们的管辖范围之内？
How was that not on our radar?
因此  在整个策划中标之后
So, after getting javelins thrown at me the entire briefing,
我就让我的团队调查这件事情
I had my team look into this.
他们在每个州  不同种族中调查  整合所有的社会经济学数据
They found it in every state, every race, across all socioeconomic data.
这在贫困偏僻的地区和传统宗教群体中十分普遍
It's common in poor and rural communities and conservative religious groups.
基督教  东正犹太教  穆斯林教  摩门教
Christian, Orthodox Jewish, Muslim, Mormon.
我的团队也分析了数据
My team ran numbers as well.
在你提到的20万起童婚中  超过三分之二的人是17岁
Of the 200,000 child marriages you mentioned, over two-thirds were 17.
还是未成年人
Still a minor.
985人是14岁  10人年仅12岁
985 of them were 14, and ten of them were only 12 years old.
这是对人权的侵犯  我要阻止它
This is a human rights violation. I want it stopped.
我可以签署一条行政命令禁止此类事件吗？
Can I sign an executive order banning it?
- 这关乎州内部的权利  - 什么权利
- It's a states' rights issue. - What's the issue?
- 童婚在这些州受法律保护   - 他们为什么不修订法律？
- Marriage is legislated by the states. - Why aren't they fixing it?
原因之一是宗教自由  婚前性行为不可饶恕
Freedom of religion, for one. Premarital sex is a sin.
你想要这些孩子在有性行为前就结婚
You want the kids married before they start having it.
当未成年少女怀孕时  许多人认为
When an underaged girl gets pregnant, many people believe
如果孩子的父母已婚的话  孩子会活得更好
the child is better off if the parents are married.
即便这个妈妈自己还是个孩子
Even if the mother is a child herself.
这还是很不合理  法律规定未满18岁就是未成年人
It's still not right. The law states you are a minor until you are 18.
我们国家保护未成年
We're a country that protects its children.
我们有相关的法律规定
We've got laws that do that.
- 我们禁止他们喝酒  抽烟  赌博
- We prevent them from drinking, smoking, gambling.
未成年不能参与投票  开立银行账户
Minors aren't allowed to vote, open a bank account.
- 租房  - 租车
- Rent an apartment. -Rent a car.
- 买烟花  - 签合同
- Buy fireworks. -Sign a contract.
他们不能雇律师  在他们离婚时可能需要
They can't hire an attorney, which they would need to get a divorce.
那我们要做些什么让这些州禁止童婚
So what do we do to get the states to ban it?
你不能在18岁这里划一条硬性分界
You can't draw a hard line at 18.
不好意思  你是哪位
I'm sorry, who are you?
伊莎贝尔·帕尔多  社会创新部部长
Isabel Pardo, director of your Office of Social Innovation.
很荣幸见到你  总统先生
It's an honor to meet you, Mr. President.
伊莎贝尔  为什么不解释一下你为何支持童婚
Isabel, why don't you explain to me why you are pro-child marriage?
我并不支持  禁止童婚的提议是我最先提出的
I'm not. Banning it was one of the first initiatives I proposed.
所以  发生了什么
So, what happened?
右翼支持斗争  我也为之准备良久
A fight from the right, which I was prepared for.
左翼有着相当的反对者  这是我没有预见的
What I didn't see coming was equal opposition from the left.
都有谁反对这件事？
Who on the left was against it?
美国公民自由协会认为婚姻本就是一项基本权利
The ACLU believes marriage is a fundamental right.
计划生育部担心这项举措会造成灾难性的下滑
Planned Parenthood fears the ban is a slippery slope.
滑坡效应我都听烦了
I am so tired of the slippery-slope argument,
尤其是用在立法之中
especially when it comes to legislation.
法律是个特例
Laws are specific.
禁止童婚与堕胎或者其他事无关
Banning child marriage wouldn't do anything to abortion or anything else.
但你还是认为我应该什么都不做
But you still think I should do nothing.
不  我认为治标应治本
No, I think you should address the root causes.
怎么做
Which are?
许多怀孕的未成年少女被父母强迫结婚
Many girls that get pregnant are coerced into getting married by their parents.
解决青少年的早孕问题
Address teen pregnancy.
命令所有公立学校提供性教育  推广避孕套
Mandate that all public schools offer sex education and access to condoms.
祝你好运
Good luck on that one.
避孕套和教育课远远不够  我们需要彻底的禁止
Condoms and classes aren't enough. We need an outright ban.
如果您想要走捷径的话  非常抱歉无法实现
If you're looking for an easy answer, there isn't one.
有的  通过一项法律
Yes, there is. Pass a law.
你还计划去南加州旅行吗
Are you still planning to travel to North Carolina?
是的  在我的发言致辞里  我会告诉美国人
Yes, I am. And in my opening comments, I will tell the American people
我打算签署一项行政命令
that I plan to sign an executive order
直击童婚的根本原因  谢谢你
that target the root causes of child marriage. Thank you.
等等
Hold on.
我正在试图阻止对印度尼西亚的森林采伐
I'm trying to prevent the complete deforestation of Indonesia
通过增加藻类的基因表达来生产棕榈油
by increasing the genetic expression of algae to produce palm oil.
目前为止黄丝藻  丝藻类和眼虫藻的发展空间最大
Tribonema, Ulothrix and euglena have the best potential so far.
我是汉娜·威尔斯
I'm Hannah Wells
我正在做关于恢复白头发的基因实验
I'm also genetically experimenting with a cure for gray hair.
你为什么愿意协助中情局呢
How would you like to come help the CIA?
绝不
Hard pass.
- 为什么  - 我是个生物骇客
- Why? - I'm a biohacker.
我们正在试图实现科学民主化
We're about the democratization of science.
- 中情局并不如此  - 某些方面
- The CIA is not. - For a reason.
正确利用生物工程  收益良多
Bioengineering in the right hands, great.
- 如果滥用  - 的确如此
-In the wrong hands - Exactly.
你知道基因编辑被列为大规模杀伤武器之一  对吗
You know gene editing is listed as a weapon of mass destruction, right?
你们并没有足够关注生物恐怖袭击
You guys aren't focused nearly enough on bioterror.
- 这是我一直关注的  - 双向摧毁已经成为过去式
- That's what I've been working on - Mutually-assured destruction is passé.
现在是生化工程的世界
- Now it's a biorogues' world.
生化武器大会并不可行甚至无法验证
The Biological Weapons Convention isn't enforceable or even verifiable.
如果你不能让大众重视  噩梦就会来临
If you don't hold people to account, shit will happen.
你需要监视每一个人
You need to be monitoring everyone.
- 就像我做的那样  - 你怎么监视每一个人
- Like I do. - How do you monitor everyone?
举个例子  我在世界各地参加生物恐怖袭击的会议
For one, I attend bioterror conferences all over the world.
我向人们介绍让我夜不能寐的东西
I give talks on things that keep me up at night.
比如说
Like what?
用我们的手机来制造生化武器将会是多么容易
How easy it's about to become to make biological weapons on our phones.
不久手机就会成为纳米组译器
They'll soon have the capability of becoming nanotech assemblers.
等到那时  你就可以利用手机打印出序列程式
And when they do, there will be sequences you can print from your phone
这足以让一整个文明崩溃
that can probably cause civilization to crash.
不论有意还是无意为之  都将会有人这样做
And someone, either intentionally or accidentally, is going to do it.
如果不加干涉  我们最终都会玩完
And without intervention, we're all ultimately screwed.
你最担心的是什么
What worries you most?
现在吗
At this moment?
这个
This.
成千上百只鸟几个月前在弗罗里达的空中坠落
Hundreds of them fell from the sky in Florida a few months back.
他们死于一种我从未见过的病毒
They died from a virus I've never seen before.
我认为是基因工程的产物
I believe it was genetically engineered.
出于何种目的
For what purpose?
这是让我夜不能寐的另外一件事
That's another thing that keeps me up at night.
好吧  那我们应该找谁谈谈
Well, who should we be talking to?
我假设那是一个尊贵的“我们”
I assume that was a royal "we."
还记得那条上级命令吗
Remember that hard pass?
你刚刚说过中情局对生物恐怖袭击的监控远远不够
-You just said that the CIA isn't doing enough to monitor bioterror,
所以帮帮我们
so help us.
我认识一个有独立实验室的生物骇客  在麻省理工学院附近
I know a biohacker with a lab near MIT
他正在做关于鸟类病毒的实验
who was experimenting with avian viruses.
诺兰·费恩
Nolan Fein.
他可不那么平易近人
He's not fed-friendly.
这么看来你能介绍我们认识就是好事儿了
- It's a good thing you're gonna be there to make the introduction.
但丁 多谢修复那个应用程序
Dontae, thank you so much for fixing that app.
- 明天我会再做检查  - 还需要再做一个β检测
- I will check it out tomorrow. - That's still being re-beta tested.
- 你得看看这个  - 是什么
- You gotta look at this. - What is it?
- 你问题的答案  - 什么问题
- The answer to your question. - What question?
为什么人们不给你投票  我想我知道原因了
Why people don't vote. I thought I knew.
我的意思是  我知道为什么我社区的有些人不投票
I mean, I know why some people in my community don't.
但我不知道这个
But I never knew this.
十个小时前  你对此放任不管
Ten hours ago, you couldn't have been more laissez-faire about this.
你发现了什么
What has gotten into you?
这个
This.
46%的选民在上一次的选举中没有投票
46% of eligible voters didn't vote in the last election.
这就是问题的关键
This is the key to why.
如果柯克曼能争取到这些选民  他就赢了
If Kirkman can get these people, he wins.
嘿 你要走吗  - 是的
Hey, are you gettin' out of here? Yes.
等着看吧
Just watch it.
但丁  你能给我找到讨论童婚的人吗
Dontae, can you find me someone talking about child marriage?
如今每个人都在讨论童婚
Everyone's talking about child marriage today.
不不不  我的意思是某个是或者曾经是未成年新娘的人
No, no, no. I mean somebody who is or was a child bride.
好的
Yeah.
要来杯喝的吗
You wanna grab a drink?
不  等等  没关系  明早的航班太早了
No, wait, nevermind. The flight is so early tomorrow.
- 发生什么事了  - 没有  我很好
- Is something going on with you? - No, I'm good.
你这一天都心不在焉
You've been distracted all day.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
你看到在屏幕上阿伦的表情了吗
Did you see Aron's face when that came up on the screen?
- 他很羞愧  - 是的
- He was mortified. - Yeah.
被选出后公之于众的羞耻
A public shaming for being singled out
作为世界上最性感的政客之一  我也会羞愧
as one of the sexiest politicians in the world. I'd be mortified.
好吧  我觉得他不喜欢被物化
Well, I don't think he likes being objectified.
我的意思是  这让他的才智和成就大打折扣
I mean, it diminishes his intellect and his actual accomplishments.
得了吧  你觉得那对一个男人的情场生活有什么帮助呢
Oh, come on. Do you have any idea what that does for a guy's dating life?
这是一种浪费  他已经有主了
It's a waste. He's off the market.
对伊莎贝尔的感情这么认真吗
It's that serious with Isabel?
办公室的人都说他们要同居了
Well, word around the office is they're moving in together.
你的妈妈怎么样
How's your mom?
她挺好的  非常好
She's good. Really good, considering.
我很久都没有像以前那样跟她好好说过话了  但是
I haven't really been talking to her as often as I should be, but
- 我有孩子了  - 什么
- I have a kid. -What?
怎么有的？ 我的意思是  我知道怎么有的  但是怎么回事
How? I mean, I know how, but how?
你不知道怎么回事
You don't know how.
当时我还是哈佛大一的学生
Um, when I was a freshman at Harvard...
我捐了我的精液
I sold my sperm.
不是吧
No.
这样来钱很快  我想都没想就做了
It was easy money. I never gave it a second thought.
她的名字是斯蒂芬妮·卡普尔  她21岁
Her name is Stephanie Kapoor. She's 21 years old.
- 这有点吓到我了  - 她怎么找到你的
- I'm kinda freaking out about it. - How did she find you?
还记得当时我在找我的亲生父母吗
-Remember when I was looking for my birth parents?
我的DNA 在DNA鉴定公司上有记录
My DNA is on 23andMe.
好吧  你就没想过你那样做的结果吗
Well, didn't you consider the consequences when you were...
为了钱对着一个小杯子射精吗？ 没有
Ejaculating into a cup for money? No, not really.
那个时候  技术还不成熟  根本没有可能
Back then, the technology didn't exist. This wasn't a possibility.
所以你什么时候见过她的
So when are you meeting her?
如果我说从没见过  我是不是糟糕透顶
Would I be a terrible person if I said never?
是的  你会是糟糕透顶
Yes, you would be a terrible, terrible person.
如果她想见你  你理应那样做
If she wants to meet you, you owe her that.
我需要来杯喝的
I do need that drink.
嘿  亲爱的
Hey, hon?
是的  我的爱人  - 这是什么
Yes, mi amor? -What is this?
训练设备
Exercise equipment.
我有跟你说过今天总统对你印象格外深刻吗
Did I mention how impressed the president was with you today?
是的  你说过了
Yes, you did.
还有我有多爱你
And how much I love you?
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我今天大获全胜  这感觉太好了
I had a big win today. It feels so good.
美国的总统
The president of the United States
即将采纳你的意见签署一份行政命令
is about to sign an executive order on your advice.
你不能再说他们不关注你了
You can't say they don't pay attention to you anymore.
副总统伊莎贝尔·帕尔多  听起来是个不错的称呼  对吗
Vice President Isabel Pardo, it kinda has a nice ring to it, right?
是的  这不会发生
Yeah, that ain't happenin'.
但是我得要跟“最英俊的政治家”一起睡觉了
But I do get to sleep with "El político más guapo."
是吗
Yeah?
这可是大不敬
Well, it would be very disrespectful
你才搬进来  今天晚上就和
for you to sleep with the prime minister of Canada tonight.
加拿大首相睡觉
You just moved in.
别因为我现在是总统就给我放水哦
Don't take it easy on me just 'cause I'm the president now.
你可得了吧  我可照看受伤的你
Lucky for you, body checking is a penalty in my league.
行行行
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你哥哥里奥昨天终于打电话回来了
Your brother Leo finally called me back yesterday.
他给让我给你打招呼
He wanted me to tell you "yo."
他会被暑期学校退学吗
Can you flunk out of summer school?
里奥挺好的  抬头往前看
Leo's doing just fine. Keep your head up and eyes forward.
嘿
Hey!
干得好
Nice check.
你知道吗  我在想
You know, I was thinking...
如果有人惹你  让你觉得不舒服
If anyone ever messed with you, made you feel uncomfortable,
你会告诉我的  对吗
you'd tell me, wouldn't you?
怎么会有人惹我  我24小时都有人保护
How can anyone mess with me? I have 24-hour protection.
对哦  是啊
Yeah, right.
是关于童养媳的事情吗
Is this about the whole child bride thing?
在日营每个人都在说这个
Everyone was talking about it at day camp.
太诡异了
It's super creepy.
是啊
Yes, it is.
得有法律禁止它
There should be a law against it.
是的
You're absolutely right.
- 光有行政命令是不够的  - 什么
- Executive order is not enough. - What?
我会尽全力让这个法律通过
I'm gonna do everything I can to help pass that law.
在这里你必须年满18周岁再结婚
You're gonna have to be 18 years old to get married in this country.
好了  现在继续  还没完呢
Now, come on. Back on your skates. We're not done.
准备好了吗
There. You ready?
你知道自从我做这份工作开始我们有什么没做吗
You know what we haven't done since I started this job?
我们连一个假期都没有休过
We haven't taken one single vacation.
我们下个月休个假吧
Let's plan one for next month.
你想去哪儿  我们就去那儿
Anywhere you wanna go, your choice.
八月的假期
It'll be August recess.
放慢步伐
It's as slow as DC gets.
我可以休一周的假  十天也可以
I can take a week, maybe even ten days.
去圣西蒙斯岛怎么样
What about St. Simons Island?
你一直想去圣西蒙斯岛  怎么样
You always loved it there at St. Simons. What do you say?
挺好的
That'll be nice.
我又回来了
I'm back.
就停这儿吧  你不用送我就去
Pop the trunk. You don't have to walk me in.
你在说什么呢  我当然要送你进去
What are you talking about? Of course I'm going to walk you in.
嘿
Hey...
我很为你骄傲
I am so proud of you.
为你自己做这些
Doing this for yourself.
我不是为了我自己
I'm not doing this for myself.
是你为了你自己让我这么做
You're making me do this for you.
28天之后再见
See you in 28 days.
当目标更伟大时
"When the goal is the greater good,
各级政府都会共同努力实现它
people from all levels of government can work together to achieve it."
你为什么不穿我给你买的衣服
Why aren't you wearing any of the clothes I brought you?
- 那些不适合我  - 是北卡罗来纳的你
- They weren't me. - It was the North Carolina you.
等我们讨论确定完他开创性的讲话之后
We need to lock down his remarks for the groundbreaking
- 他就都是你的  - 行吧
- and then he's all yours. - Fine.
本着这种精神我计划
"It is in this spirit that I plan
立法禁止童婚
to introduce legislation to ban child marriage,
制定联邦法律  规定最低年龄是18岁
establish federal law that makes 18 the minimum age--"
- 你不能这么说  - 为什么
- No, you can't say that. - Why not?
各州权利  宗教权利  父母权利
States' rights, religious rights, parental rights.
- 你到底在干什么啊  - 拯救受虐儿童啊
- What the fuck are you doing? - Saving abused children.
你为什么反对这个
How can you possibly have a problem with that?
- 因为这会让他输掉选举的  - 胡说
- Because it'll cost him the election! - That's insane.
数据表明
I have polling data that says
反对童婚的人比支持的多
a hell of a lot more people are against child marriage than for it.
那些数据不能说明什么
That data doesn't mean anything.
反对它的人不会因为这个投你
The people that are against it, it's not an issue they vote on.
但是支持童婚的人
But the people who don't want the ban,
那些会被这项禁令影响到的人
the people who are personally affected by it,
我敢打赌他们每一个人
you can bet your ass that every single one of them
都会站出来反对你
will show up to vote against you.
- 这是正确的事情  - 这是下意识的反应
- It's the right thing to do. - This is a knee-jerk reaction.
你只是因为尴尬这么做
You're doing this out of embarrassment.
她当然不在乎童婚  他们还没有投票的权利
She could give a shit about child brides. They aren't old enough to vote.
别这么做  这毫无意义
Please don't shoot yourself in the dick. It's pointless.
国会甚至不会考虑这个问题
Congress won't even take this up.
你有能力和途径帮那些女孩儿们
You have the power and the platform to help these girls.
童养媳大都不在学校学习
Child brides are less likely to stay in school,
她们更有可能在遭受家庭暴力
more likely to experience domestic violence.
她们百分之三十一的人相当贫穷
They're 31% more likely to end up in poverty.
而大部分最后都离婚了
The majority of them end up in divorce.
讲你不可能通过的立法
Introducing legislation that you cannot possibly push through,
这什么都不能给你  你会满盘皆输
it gets you nothing and costs you everything.
你想要赢还是输
Do you wanna win or not?
赛斯  你觉得呢
Seth, what do you think?
- 她们都有道理  - 胆小鬼
- They're both right. - Pussy.
但丁找了个女人
Dontae found me this woman.
你决定之前看完这个
Watch it before you decide.
这是我  结婚前一年的我
That was me, the school year prior to marriage.
13岁的时候  我被性侵了
At 13, I was sexually assaulted.
新学年要开始的时候
As the upcoming school year started,
我发现我怀孕了
then I found out that I was pregnant.
然后因为宗教原因  我嫁给了那个男人
And, given the religious community, I had to marry this person.
我女儿两岁的时候  他就开始虐待她
When my daughter was two, he became abusive to her.
所以我抓起女儿逃了出去
And so I grabbed her and ran to get away from him.
我敲别人的门  没人让我进去
And I would knock on somebody's door, and nobody would let me in.
然后我抱着我的孩子
And I'd hide in the creek...
躲到了溪里面
holding my baby.
好消息  你猜怎么着  灭虫员把老鼠弄走了
Good news on the you-know-what. The exterminator showed up and got it.
干得好  菲利克斯  前途一片光明啊
Well done, Felix. Your future's looking markedly brighter.
现在是坏消息
And now the bad news.
是法律规定了好消息必须带坏消息吗
Is there a law that good news has to come with bad?
灭虫员找到了老鼠洞
The exterminator located the hole where the mouse got in.
那个洞是白蚁造成的
The hole was caused by termites.
- 我们不能把白宫围起来灭虫  - 我会想办法的
- We are not tenting the White House. - I'll look into options.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
要是今天天气更好些就好了
I wish we could've brought you better weather.
但是今天是吉祥的日子
But this is an auspicious day.
事实证明当目标是更大的善时
Proof that when the goal is the greater good,
各级政府会为实现它共同努力
people from all levels of government can work together to achieve it.
本着这种精神
And it is in that spirit...
本着这种精神  我的同伴们
It is in that spirit that my partners here on the dais,
政府各方的代表
representatives of all aspects of the government
我们的私人投资者共同努力
and our private sector investors have worked together,
不仅要建立一座新桥
not only to build a new bridge,
还要确保旧桥的悲剧不会降临到
but to ensure that the tragedy of the old one
这个伟大国家的另外一座城市
never befalls another city in this great nation.
很荣幸我们今天来参加这个奠基仪式
It is with great honor that we break ground here today.
他甚至提都没提
He didn't even bring it up.
伊西  我很抱歉  我不知道发生了什么
I'm sorry, Isi. I don't know what happened.
我知道  他变成了一个政客
I do. He became a politician.
我没投票  我很自豪
I didn't vote and I'm kinda proud of that
因为我不喜欢那个竞选的人
because I did not like the person that was running for office.
我被逮捕了  最后承认犯有重罪
I was arrested, ended up pleading guilty to a felony count.
认识到我是重罪犯几个月之后
Couple of months after realizing that I was a felon,
我知道我失去了投票权
I realized I lost the right to vote.
以为是周二
With it being on a Tuesday,
我在学习上学  还有两份兼职
I work two jobs and go to school full time,
我没时间去投票
so I don't have the availability to just leave to go vote.
我只是觉得我不了解我要投的人
I just didn't feel like I had the informed opinion about who I was voting for.
没有人能代表我
And I don't feel like anybody represents me personally.
两党制是行不通的
The two-party system doesn't work
除了共和党和民主党  我们需要更多的选择
because we need more options to vote other than just Republican or Democratic.
如果有第三个党派的候选人
If we had a third-party candidate who had a fighting chance,
那我更倾向于投他
then I'd be more inclined to vote for that person.
嘿
Hey.
我知道我让你失望了
I know I disappointed you.
你这么做我能理解
I understand why you did it.
我不确定我能不能
I'm not sure I do.
这不意味着我放过你了
Doesn't mean I'm letting you off the hook.
一旦你当选了  你得好好干
Once you're elected, you have to make good on it.
我会的  我保证
I will, I promise.
谢谢你的理解
Thank you for understanding.
我是理解你  所以我要离开白宫
I do, and it's why I need to leave the White House.
艾米丽  不要
Emily, please.
我需要你
I need you.
我知道你需要我  所以我才要离开
I know you do, and that's why I need to leave.
- 我要去竞选部  - 和罗琳吗
- I want to move to the campaign. -With Lorraine?
是的
Exactly.
你不信任她
You don't trust her.
那你信任她吗
Do you?
晚上好  怀特先生
Good evening, Mr. Wright.
你好  我想打个电话给斯蒂芬妮·卡普尔
Hi. I'd like to make a phone call please, to Stephanie Kapoor.
区号是3-8-0
The number is area code 3-8-0...
5-5-5
5-5-5...
0-1-8
0-1-8...
最后一位是多少  怀特先生  你还在吗
And the final digit? Mr. Wright, are you there?
是你的前女友因为那本杂志给你打电话了吗
If that's a booty call from one of your exes because of that magazine...
怎么回事
What?
- 罗琳  - 亚伦  我们能谈谈吗
- Lorraine? - Aaron. Can we talk?
现在可不是好时候
Actually, right now is not a good time at all, really.
那明天一大早到竞选办公室来
Come by the campaign office first thing in the morning.
再考虑一下你是否愿意成为
And think about whether you'd like to join the ticket
科尔曼的副总统
as Kirkman's vice president.
佩妮  你怎么还没睡
Penny, what are you still doing awake?
我在等你
I waited up for you.
要布丁吗
Pudding?
当然
Sure, why not?
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
北卡罗来纳怎么样了
How was North Carolina?
北卡罗来纳  资金筹集推迟了
North Carolina, well... The fundraiser went late.
你宣布了你的新法律了吗
Did you announce your new law?
没  还没呢  宝贝儿
No. Not yet, sweetheart.
为什么
Why?
因为所以
Just 'cause.
费恩博士的安全级别比你高一些
Dr. Fein's security is a little higher than yours.
这些是去年新换的
It's new from last year.
他车在外面呢  他一定在这里
His car was outside. He has to be here.
好吧  他可能受伤了
All right, then maybe he's hurt.
退后
You know what? Step back.
我可以
Or I could just, uh...
现在我真的想要和你朋友谈谈
Now I really wanna talk to your friend.
这没道理啊
This makes no sense.
为什么他搬空了实验室却把车留下了
Why would he take his entire lab but leave his car?
他没离开
Well, he wouldn't.
整个实验室都被漂白剂擦过了
This entire place has been scrubbed with bleach.
你知道他可能在哪儿吗
Do you know where he could be?
不知道
No.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177
本集中所用到的真人采访画面都由纪录片影人提供
他们的观点没有剧本支持 均为个人观点
视频剪辑标准为内容和时长